嘿
Hey.
Hi 放映会怎么样啊?
Hi, how was the screening?
著名黑人平权活动家
这个嘛 Sheldon引用了Rosa Parks的例子
Oh, Sheldon invoked Rosa Parks
让一个插队的人自惭形秽
to make somebody who cut the line feel bad,
但只有白人觉得愧疚罢了
but only the white people felt bad.
唉 我真不该给他买那本介绍
Ugh, I should've never bought him that coloring book
黑人历史月的填色簿的
that explains Black History Month.
你和我妈妈相处得怎么样?
How'd it go with my mother?
刚开始的时候是有点不顺
Uh, you know, it started a little rocky,
但我想我们后来还是达成共识了
but I think we got to a good place.
哇哦
Wow.
不错啊
Well done.
之后我送她回酒店的时候
Yeah, and when I dropped her off at the hotel,
她还给了我一个拥抱呢
she even gave me a hug.
她是不是觉得你噎住了还是...
Did she think you were choking or...
不好意思 这真是太棒了
I'm sorry, that's great.
谢谢你花时间来陪她
Thank you for spending time with her.
别客气
No problem.
对了
Um, so listen,
我不知道你下周末有没有什么计划
I don't know if you have any plans next weekend,
但我答应了你母亲
but I kind of promised your mom
要再举行一次婚礼仪式
we'd have another wedding ceremony
这一次她就能来参加了
so she could attend this time.
你是说我们要再结一次婚?
Wait, we're gonna get married again?
算是吧 但这一次我们可以叫上家人和朋友
Yeah, kind of, but now we can invite our friends and family.
真是一个拥抱带来的灾难啊
Seems like a lot of trouble for a hug.
别这样嘛 一定会很有趣的
Come on, it'll be fun,
你知道吗 我们第一次结婚没有邀请你妈妈
and, you know, your mom was genuinely hurt
她真的很受伤
we didn't invite her to the first one.
站在我们的角度
Look, in our defense,
这是一时兴起决定去做的事情
it was kind of a spur of the moment thing,
而且我们不喜欢她
and also, we don't like her.
Leonard 她毕竟是你妈妈啊
Leonard, come on, she's your mom.
如果我们能做点什么让她开心的话
If we can do something to make her happy,
何乐而不为呢?
why wouldn't we?
我不是刚刚才说了原因吗
I just said why...
我们对她没爱啊
we don't like her.
那这样吧 别管她了
Hey, look, then forget about her,
就当是为了我们自己
let's do it for us.
我们不用搞得特别隆重正规
We could keep it small and informal.
这一次我们叫上我们的家人
This time we can invite our families.
你兄弟出狱了吗?
Is your brother out of prison?
监狱人满为患了 托福啊
Thanks to overcrowding, yeah.
我真希望我爸爸能来
I'd love it if my dad could come.
你一定要邀请他
Oh, you have to invite him.
自从他离婚以后我就没见过他了
I haven't seen him since the divorce.
他像变了一个人一样
Oh, he's like a different man.
他的抽搐停止了
Oh. He stopped twitching,
我觉得他还长高了一尺半呢
and I think he grew an inch and a half.
那就这么说定了
Well, then it's settled.
好吧
Yay.
天哪
God.
真是太搞笑了
So funny.
我从没想过第二次结婚对象还是你这货
I never thought my second marriage would be to you!
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第九季24集 季终集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 想和Bucky一起写手帐的沫纸
校对: UUUUUU放假不放假有区别吗
翻译: 李小宝Licht  舒大卷子  無限月讀
这不是一次法律意义上的仪式
Okay, so it's not a legal ceremony,
这只是提供了一次机会
it's just a chance for us
让我们在重读誓言时能有你们的陪伴
to redo our vows so everyone can be part of it.
所以也就没有伴娘了?
So there's no maid of honor?
没有
No.
呵呵
Huh.
但假如我穿着一条紫色的缎子裙
But if I were to, say, wear a purple satin dress
戴着心形项链站在你旁边
with a sweetheart neckline and stand near you,
你也不能阻止我对吧?
you wouldn't be able to stop me, right?
当然不能了
I don't see how I could.
那我就大方地答应你吧
Then I graciously accept.
谁来主持呢?
Who's going to officiate?
我希望你能来主持
I was kind of hoping you would.
等等 那我现在只是个逊到爆的伴娘了吗?
Wait, now I'm just some lousy maid of honor?
嘿 好消息 我刚和我妈打完电话
Hey, good news, I just got off the phone with my mother.
她要来参加你们的婚礼
She is coming to the wedding.
好吧 先别急
Okay, wait,
你邀请别人来参加我们的婚礼?
you're inviting people to our wedding?
是啊 我邀请别人来参加“我们的”婚礼
Yes, I'm inviting people to our wedding.
我还顺便问了
Yeah, I've already asked
史蒂芬·霍金和小罗伯特唐尼
Stephen Hawking and Robert Downey Jr.
不过你也不要抱太大希望 因为他真的很忙
And now, don't get your hopes up, 'cause he's pretty busy,
还有Erno Rubik
but Erno Rubik.
谁是Erno Rubik?
Who's Erno Rubik?
你真的不知道吗?
Seriously?
他可是发明魔方的人呢
He invented the Rubik's Cube.
好吧
Okay, fine,
但你为什么要请他来参加我们的婚礼?
but why would you invite him to our wedding?
因为除了他的名声和财富之外
Because, despite his fame and fortune,
他独行侠的身姿震慑了我
he strikes me as a lonely man.
你能为Leonard的妈妈
Well, it's very sweet
不怕麻烦地筹划这些事情真是周到
of you to go to all this trouble for Leonard's mother.
是啊 我这么做也是为了Leonard
Yeah, I'm also doing it for Leonard.
我想这对他们之间的关系会很有帮助
I think this could really help their relationship.
你怎么敢在征询我的意见之前就先邀请你爸爸!
How dare you invite your father without consulting me!
我很抱歉 但我觉得我不需要得到你的允许
Sorry, but I don't think I need your permission
才能邀请我的父亲参加我的婚礼
to have my father at my wedding.
你也知道我们的婚姻之所以结束是因为他有了外遇
You do understand our marriage ended because he had an affair.
我知道
I know,
外遇没有借口
and there's no excuse for that.
他说我冷漠 不近人情
He claimed I was cold, emasculating,
而且这么多年来从未对他产生过任何生理上的吸引
and hadn't shown him any physical affection for years.
我错了 这段外遇确实事出有因啊
I was wrong, there's three excuses for that.
额滴神那
Oh, my God.
成功了
It's working.
你确定吗?
You sure?
看
Look.
这个系统正在维持自己的稳定性
The system is maintaining its own stability,
量子涡旋装置正在控制自己的方向
the quantum vortex apparatus is now controlling the orientation.
没错
You're right.
你明白这意味着什么的吧?
You realize what this means?
是啊
Yeah.
我明白
I do.
这证明了一个概念
It's proof of concept.
我们找到了可行的导航系统了
We've got a workable guidance system.
恭喜恭喜
Congratulations.
谢谢你!
Thanks!
嘿
Hey,
我刚刚受到了美国空军发来的邮件
I just got an e-mail from the U.S. Air Force.
打开看看
Open it.
唔...
Hmm.
我们希望能在您空闲时尽快和您会面
"We request a meeting at your earliest convenience
商谈关于您的量子导航系统的
"regarding your quantum guidance system,
暂时性专利62/295118号
provisional patent 62/295118."
这还真是奇怪
That's weird.
我们被我们不知道的小窗秘密监视了吗?
Is there a window around here we don't know about?
我想这应该只是巧合
I'm sure it's just a coincidence.
是啊
Yeah, of course.
不然还能是什么呢?
What else could it be?
兄弟们 我爱米国哦
Boy, do I love America.
谢谢你来接我
Thank you for picking me up.
别客气
Oh, you're welcome.
我是在和你的小女友说话呢
I was speaking to your young lady.
荣幸之至 Cooper夫人
My pleasure, Mrs. Cooper.
叫我Mary就好了
Oh, please call me Mary.
好吧 Mary
Okay, Mary.
本宝宝对这称呼不爽
You know, that doesn't work for me,
还是叫Cooper夫人好了
let's stay with Mrs. Cooper.
Sheldon 别犯傻
Sheldon, don't be silly.
怎么了?
Wait, what?
在我了解你之前我都是这么叫你的
That's what I called you till I got to know you better.
Leonard和Penny能邀请我真是太贴心了
It was so nice of Leonard and Penny to invite me.
- 实际上 是我...  - 是啊
- Well, actually, I...  - It sure was.
Leonard在我心里一直有特殊的位置
I've always had a special place in my heart for Leonard.
照顾我的宝贝这么多年
Taking care of my baby all these years.
打断一下
Excuse me,
是我照顾他
I take care of him.
当然啦
Sure you do.
还有谁会来参加这个聚会?
So who else is coming to this shindig?
还是那群人
Oh, well, the usual gang.
Penny的家人明天来
Penny's family is coming tomorrow.
Leonard的妈妈已经到了
Yeah, and Leonard's mother's already here.
哦 Beverly
Oh, Beverly.
太好了
How nice.
你见过她吧?
You've met her, right?
是的 我见过
Yes, I have.
妈妈 她是无神论者
Mother, she's an atheist,
不是吸血鬼
not a vampire.
不管怎样 我们停车去找点大蒜
Either way, let's stop and get some garlic.
Mary 你最近怎么样?
So, Mary, how have you been?
谢谢关心
Well, thank you so much for asking.
我很好 你呢?
I've been well, and you?
- 很好  - 好的
- Very good.  - Good.
我不知道
I don't know what
我们在担心什么 她们相处的很好
we were worried about, they're getting along great.
Sheldon告诉我你的老公要来
Sheldon tells me your husband's coming.
我的前任老公
My ex-husband.
不好意思
Oh, I'm so sorry.
不需要
Don't be.
好吧
All right.
好冷啊
Whew, chilly.
我都看到我呼出来的气了
I think I can see my breath.
我们可以听到
We can hear you.
- 对不起  - 对不起
- Sorry.  - Sorry.
简直不相信我会这么天真
I can't believe I was so naive.
军方要
The military is just gonna
接管整个项目
take over the whole project.
你知道如果拒绝会怎样吗?
And you know what happens if we object?
我们会消失
We disappear.
从地图上消失
Like off the map.
就像第四季之后的美国偶像冠军们一样
Like every American Idol winner since season four.
Howard 你反应过度啦
Come on, Howard, you're overreacting.
我有吗?
Am I?
有吗?
要打赌吗 一些秘密工作者
Wha... what do you want to bet some black ops guy
正在重新打印我的高中年鉴
is reprinting my high school yearbook
而我不在里面?
and I'm no longer in it?
象棋俱乐部的照片现在
That chess club picture is now
只剩下David Zimmerman和Elaine Cho了
just David Zimmerman and Elaine Cho.
我在浏览空军网站
Okay, look, I'm on the Air Force Web site,
给你发邮件的部门
and the department that e-mailed you
是负责收购的
is in charge of acquisitions.
也许他们只是想给你
So maybe they just want to give you
一些钱资助你的发明
a lot of money for your invention.
得了吧 他们不是这样的
Oh, please, that's not how it works.
你看过ET 阿凡达 侏罗纪公园
You saw E.T., Avatar, Jurassic World.
军方只是出现然后接管
The military just shows up and takes over.
你知道这些不是纪录片吧?
You do realize those weren't documentaries, right?
你觉得这很好笑?
I'm sorry, you find this funny?
不是 我只是在想侏罗纪公园
No, I was just thinking about Jurassic World.
太恐怖了
Boy, that was terrible.
我们必须走楼梯
Oh, we have to use the stairs.
他们什么时候修电梯?
When are they gonna fix your elevator?
我不...随时都有可能
Uh... I don't... any day now.
走楼梯挺好
Well, the stairs are fine.
而且 你妈就在上面
Besides, your mother is up there.
我可能会心脏病发作 那就不用见她了
Maybe I'll have a heart attack and not have to see her.
我知道你和妈妈的关系
Hey, I, I know things are a little rough
有点僵
with you and Mom,
但我很高兴你来了
but I'm really glad you're here.
我也是
Me, too.
我不应该做血管成形术的 因为我感觉很好
I should have never had that angioplasty because I feel fine.
Penny很想见到你
Penny's really looking forward to seeing you.
她是个甜心
Ah, she's a sweetie.
你娶了一个好的 Leonard
You got a good one there, Leonard.
谢谢 爸爸
Thanks, Dad.
你他妈是怎么做到的?
How the hell did you do that?
是不是很美好?
Isn't this nice?
我们到啦
Hey, we're here.
啊Alfred!
Alfred!
谢谢你的到来!
Thank you for coming! Oh.
很高兴来到这里
Well, happy to be here.
- 恭喜  - 谢谢
- And congratulations.  - Thank you.
爸 你还记得Sheldon
Dad, you remember Sheldon.
Hofstadter博士
Dr. Hofstadter.
Cooper博士
Dr. Cooper.
- 这是Sheldon的妈妈 Mary  - 你好
- This is Sheldon's mother, Mary.  - How do you do?
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
他的女朋友 Amy
And his girlfriend, Amy.
- 幸会  - 你好
- A pleasure.  - Hi.
还有 当然啦 妈妈
And, of course, Mom.
你好 可恨的悍妇
Hello, my hateful shrew.
你好 老王八
Hello to you, you wrinkled old bastard.
好吧 我开始觉得气氛有点紧张了
All right, now I'm starting to sense a little tension.
你们俩别说了
All right, you two, don't start.
Penny和我是为了你们举办第二场婚礼
Penny and I are throwing this second wedding for your benefit.
请你们不要毁了它好吗?
Can you please not ruin it?
当然 对不起
Of course. I'm sorry.
看看 你可以道歉的嘛
Oh, look at that-- you can apologize.
- 妈!  - 对不起
- Mom!  - I'm sorry.
圣经上讲宽恕...
You know, the Bible says forgiveness...
- 妈!  - 对不起
- Mom!  - I'm sorry.
有谁饿了?
Uh, who's hungry?
我们在城里最好的餐馆定了位子
We have a reservation at the best restaurant in town.
在大众点评上只有三颗半星
It only got three-and-a-half stars on Yelp.
- Sheldon!  - 我没错 这是事实
- Sheldon!  - I'm not sorry. That's true.
我不知道怎么办
I don't know what to do.
他们是空军
It's the Air Force.
我应该回邮件吗?
I mean, should I respond to their e-mail?
或者忽略它?
Ignore it?
你不能忽略它
You can't ignore it.
这可不是通知
It's not that postcard that says it's time
你该去看牙医的明信片
to go back to the dentist.
同志们 快点
Guys, come on.
我们要去和大家一起吃晚饭了
We're meeting everyone for dinner.
等等 我害怕
One sec. I'm just afraid
如果我回复了 他们就会知道我收到了
if I respond, then they'll know I got it.
哥们
Oh, dude.
当你打开邮件的时候
The minute you opened that e-mail,
他们就知道你收到了
they knew you got it.
他们可能正在通过
I mean, they're probably looking at you
摄像头看你
through the camera right now. Oh, damn.
我爱美国
I love America.
你们胡说八道够了吗?
Are you done with this nonsense?
这不是胡说
It's not nonsense.
美国军方就是这样的
This is how the U.S. military works.
如果是美国军方
Oh, if it's even the U.S. military.
可能是外国的军方假装成美国的
It could be foreign military pretending to be American.
你说得对 我们把引导系统交给他们
You're right. We turn our guidance system over to them,
然后 他们就会使用它来对付我们
next thing we know, they're using it against us.
我也爱美国的敌人
I also love the enemies of America.
Penny 我希望我和Leonard他爸
Penny, I hope the example of my failed marriage
失败的婚姻不会
to Leonard's father doesn't discourage you
影响你们俩彼此许下的承诺
from the commitment you've made to one another.
当然不会
Oh, of course not.
尽管Alfred和我比你们俩经历的更多
Although Alfred and I had a lot more going for us than you two.
妈 留点话做祝酒词吧
Mom, please save something for the toast.
Alfred 你是做什么的?
So, Alfred, what is it that you do for a living?
我是一个人类学家
Oh, I'm an anthropologist.
我研究古代的人和文化
I study ancient peoples and cultures.
天哪 就是追溯到大洪水时代
My goodness, so all the way back to the Flood.
别笑 她不是开玩笑的
Don't laugh... she wasn't joking.
你玩手机吧
Play with your phone.
关于这一点
Well, on that note,
在许多文化中有天启的洪水
there are many cultures that have an apocalyptic flood
作为他们神话的一部分
as part of their mythology.
我没有神话
I don't have a mythology.
我说的是上帝的真言
I have the unerring Word of God.
但是那很有意思
But that's very interesting.
噢
Oh.
我不是要贬损你的信仰
I-I didn't mean to disparage your faith.
其实我很崇尚它
Actually, I admire it.
- 真的吗?  - 是的
- Really?  - Yes.
我自己也是不可知论者
Yes, I'm an agnostic myself,
我也向上帝祈求过很多次
but I have prayed, many times, to God,
把我老婆变成一根盐柱子
to turn my wife into a pillar of salt.
其实他做的也差不多呀
Well, He came close.
他把她变成一大块冰块了
Turned her into a giant block of ice.
Howard 你肯定可以
Howard, there must be someone at the university
向学校里的什么人求助啊
you can go to for help.
你搞笑呢吧?
Are you kidding?
很可能就是他们
They're probably the ones who leaked it
首先泄露给军方的
to the military in the first place.
新闻第四频道的那个家伙呢?
What about the guy on the Channel Four News?
就是"身边的第四频道"?
You know, "Four on Your Side"?
也许他可以在你身边支持你
Maybe he can be on your side.
我正被政府困扰
I'm being harassed by the government,
而不是要调查什么遛狗时的骗术
not trying to get to the bottom of a dog-walking scam.
别扯淡了!
Oh, stop!
你知道怎么回事吗?
You know what's really happening?
你们看过的那些电影
All the movies you've watched,
电视剧 漫画书...
the TV shows, the comic books...
那些东西扭曲了你们的想法
they've completely twisted your thinking.
没人跟踪你们 没人窃听你们
No one's after you, no one's listening to you,
根本就没人在乎你们
no one cares about you.
我还是宁可认为
I'd like to think
"身边的第四频道"是在乎我的
the "Four on Your Side" guy cares about me.
你看 Beverly 我了解你和Alfred之间
You know, Beverly, I know you and Alfred
有分歧 但是想一想
have your differences, but if you think about it,
如果没有和他结婚 就不会有Leonard了
if you hadn't married him, there'd be no Leonard.
还是不错的 对吧?
So that's good, right?
切
Eh.
我们前面的是Howard吗?
Is that Howard in front of us?
也许吧
Oh, maybe.
开近一点
Get closer.
天啊
Oh, God.
我觉得有人在跟踪我们
I think someone's following us.
你在瞎扯
You're being ridiculous.
我没有瞎扯... 他就在我后面
I'm not being ridiculous... he's right on my tail.
在这里左转 看看会不会跟着我们
Uh, turn left here and see if he turns with us.
为什么在这里转弯?
Well, why is he turning here?
餐厅在另一个方向 我也不知道
The restaurant's the other way. I don't know.
他有查路况的手机软件 也许前面有事故
He uses that traffic app. Maybe there's an accident.
那就跟着他
Oh, so follow him.
别啊!
Oh, no!
我就说!
I told you!
也许只是碰巧
It's probably just a coincidence.
开快点 看他会不会跟上来
Speed up a little, see if he stays with you.
开快点
Well, go faster.
你要跟丢了 他这么急干什么?
You're losing him. What is his hurry?
这么着 闪一下车灯
You know what, flash your lights.
让他知道是你
Let him know it's you.
他在闪车灯
He's flashing his lights.
那是什么意思?
What's that mean?
也许他想让我们停车
I... I think he wants us to pull over.
别停车!
Do not pull over!
我可不想一个人养这个孩子!
I'm not raising this baby alone!
坐稳了!
Hang on!
你丈夫过世后
So, after your husband passed,
你没再婚过?
you never remarried?
没有 只专注于工作和教堂的事务
No, just focused on work and the church.
你在哪儿工作?
Ah. And what do you do?
在教堂里
I work at the church.
有你真帮了他们大忙
Well, they're lucky to have you.
谢谢
Well, thank you.
别在意
You're welcome.
你了解这是什么情况吗?
Do you realize what's happening here?
我了解
Yeah, I do.
他们只吃面包 没法吃正餐了
They're filling up on bread and ruining their meal.
- 嘿  - 嘿
- Hey.  - Hey.
你们怎么这时候才来?
What took you guys so long?
我们跟着Howard 可不知为什么
Oh, we were following Howard, but for some reason,
他关了头灯 上了一条单行道
he turned off his headlights and went up a one-way street.
你们聊得怎么样?
So, what did we miss?
Mary和我互相了解了一下
Oh, just Mary and I getting to know each other a little.
Leonard 你父亲很有意思
Leonard, your father is just charming.
他还破产了
He's also broke.
他提过吗?
Did he mention that?
得了 老妈 你坐那边去...
Okay, Mom, you sit over there...
我给Bernadette打电话 看看他们碰上什么了
And I'm gonna call Bernadette and see what's keeping them.
我不知道你破产了
If I'd known you were broke,
我不该对面包的事情大惊小怪
I wouldn't have made a big deal about the bread.
喂 Penny
Hey, Penny.
你说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
刚才是你?
Oh, that was you?
说来话长
Long story.
你们先吃吧
Why don't you go ahead and eat.
我们还要一会儿
We're gonna be a while.
我跟你讲 我没嗑药
I'm telling you, I'm not on drugs.
政府正要抓住我!
The government's out to get me!
最近最有意思的发现之一就是
Now, one of the more exciting things to be found recently
尼安德特人
is that Neanderthals
和智人曾经经常通婚
and Homo sapiens frequently mated with each other.
那正好解释了我和Sheldon父亲的婚姻
Well, that certainly explains my marriage to Sheldon's father.
笑点在于我父亲不是个聪明人
That's funny, because my father was not a very clever man.
你不解释我还真不知道呢
I'd be lost without you.
我来祝一下酒
Uh, I would like to propose a toast
向我的妻子和准新娘
to my wife and bride-to-be.
这里的笑点在于...
See, that's funny because...
玩你的电话去
Back to your phone.
Penny啊...
Penny...
我确信自己一直都爱你
I've always known I loved you,
但过去的一年让我明白
but this last year has shown me
和你结婚让我更幸福
that I also love being married to you.
谢谢你嫁给我
Thank you for saying yes.
谢谢你坚持不懈的求婚
Oh, thanks for asking until I did.
干杯
Hear, hear.
Cheers.
我也要祝酒
I, uh, I would also like to make a toast.
噢
Aw.
Leonard啊
Leonard,
我很高兴你找到了一个
I am so happy that you have found a woman
爱你关心你的女人
who loves and cares for you.
你那是什么意思?
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
你吃药了吗?
Why don't you take a pill?
就像你行房前来一片那样?
Like you did before sex?
我真正需要的
What I really needed
其实是把眼睛蒙起来
was a blindfold.
好了 大家...
All right, everyone...
冷静些
calm down.
让我们都记住圣经里的话:
Let's all remember what it says in the Bible:
贤者慎怒
"He who is slow to anger
宽宏大量
is better than the mighty."
亲爱的 你能读本别的书吗?
Oh, dear woman, can you please read another book?
如果是上帝写的 我就读
When God writes one, I will.
如果有人想吃蛋酥
Um, if... if we want to order the soufflé,
我们该点了
we might want to get on that.
Leonard 如果不介意的话 我有点累了
Leonard, if you don't mind, I think I'm a little tired.
今晚就到这儿吧
I'm gonna call it a night.
好的 老爸
Sure, Dad.
我累坏了
I'm a little tuckered out myself,
大家明天早上见吧
so I will see you all in the morning.
要一起坐车吗?
Would you like to share a cab?
好啊
That would be fine.
- 你住哪儿?  - 威斯汀饭店
- Where are you staying?  - I'm at the Westin.
我也是
Oh, so am I.
要一起吃宵夜吗?
Can I interest you in a nightcap?
好主意
I think that you could.
发生什么了?
What is happening there?
很明显啊
I think it's pretty obvious.
他们不想吃甜点 因为面包吃多了
They don't want dessert 'cause they filled up on bread.
她没接电话
She's still not answering.
我爸也没回消息
My father's not texting me back.
他俩电话都关机了
'Cause they both turned their phones off.
我可不喜欢这样
I don't like this at all.
我也不喜欢
I don't like it either.
真的?
Really?
我简直开心得不行啊
'Cause I love it.